braintrack.com 2014-05-11

# Privacy Policy - BrainTrack.com

The purpose of BrainTrack.com’ privacy statement is to clarify how BrainTrack.com engages in procuring, using, and sharing users’ personal information they provide to our website.

#### Privacy Statement Changes 

BrainTrack.com’s privacy policy may change from time-to-time to exhibit changes we make to our information procuring, using, or sharing practices. We advise checking this page occasionally to maintain a current comprehension of said policy.

#### Information We Collect 

While you use our website and services, BrainTrack.com may collect the personal information listed below: 

  * Contact Information: Your first and last name and the various means by which we can contact you, such as your email address, telephone number, etc.
  * Demographic Information: Your gender, educational background, location, etc. 
  * Computer Information: Your IP address, operating system, etc. 

#### Information We Use

This information is gathered by BrainTrack.com to provide the following services for users: 

  * Online degree recommendations that fit your goals and/or needs.
  * Information relating to your personal career and education goals.
  * Information relating specifically to schools that offer flexible programs that may meet your needs, and/or that you have requested information on.
  * Customer service for requests, questions, or concerns you’ve expressed
  * Newsletter communications
  * Marketing communications 

Additionally, information is gathered to help in BrainTrack.com’s business development efforts, such as our marketing and web improvement endeavors, and to engage in research and analysis to meet our business goals.

####  Opting-Out of Marketing Communications 

BrainTrack.com may send you marking communications. If you do not want to receive such communications, you have the option to opt-out of them. You may do this by following the instructions for unsubscribing, which are included in emails.

#### Information We Share

This section of the privacy policy stands to inform users of the circumstances in which will share their personal information with third parties; as such, we will only share your personal information in accordance to this policy. Under no circumstance will BrainTrack.com sell users’ personal information to third parties for their own, impertinent marketing practices.

One instance in which BrainTrack.com may share your personal information is if any portion of its assets are merged, acquisitioned, or sold and the law requires such sharing. With users’ prior consent, BrainTrack.com may confer their personal information to a third party in this situation when we, in good faith, believe it crucial to do so to:

  * Uphold BrainTrack.com’s rights
  * Guarantee protection for your well-being or others’
  * Investigate fraud
  * Heed a request made by the government

Another instance when BrainTrack.com may share users’ personal information with a third party is when it is necessary for business activities to which BrainTrack.com contracts service companies to complete. Examples of such companies are a third party customer or email service provider.

Important also for users to know is that in providing BrainTrack.com with your personal information, you are legally querying our services. As such, you give us, our business affiliates, and our third party marketing affiliates consent to contact you. This consent extends to telephone contact regardless of users’ participation in state or federal Do Not Call lists; a query legally equates to an exemption from all Do No Call requirements.

#### Contacting BrainTrack.com 

Questions or concerns about BrainTrack.com’s privacy policy can be submitted using our contact form. 

This privacy policy is effective as of August 18, 2012
